appmakr.com 2013-05-21

# AppMakr :: Publish your own iPhone apps for free!

**AppMakr** **Privacy Policy**

Last updated on October 24th, 2011.

AppMakr is an online platform (the “Service”) provided by Socialize, Inc., f.k.a. PointAbout, Inc. (the “Company,” “we”), on AppMakr.com that acts as a portal through which developers (the “Developers,” “you”) can create mobile applications (the “Apps”) with various types of media for their end users (the “End-Users”). This Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") describes the privacy practices that the Company employs with regard to information, including personal information, that it collects and receives from Developers and End-Users who use or access the Service.

**Third-Party Websites and Links** ****

You may be directed to other sites that are developed and administered by people or companies not affiliated with the Company. Such third party sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of such third parties. You are responsible for reviewing any third-party site's privacy policy, as it may be different from this Privacy Policy. The Company is not responsible for the actions of such third parties, the content of their sites, the use of information you provide to such third parties, or any products or services they may offer. Any link to such third party sites on the Service does not constitute the Company’s sponsorship of, or affiliation with, such third parties.Additionally, this Privacy Policy does not govern the privacy practices of the Developers and Developer Apps created using the Service, as the Developers and Developer Apps are not controlled by the Company. However, Developers are bound by the Company’s Terms of Service in order to use the Service. It is expected that Developers respect the privacy of their End-users, but the Company cannot be held responsible for the actions and practices of the Developers. 

**Consent** ****

By registering with or submitting information through our Service, Developers and their End-Users agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and they expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of their information, including personal information made available in use of the Service, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Information Collection and Use** ****

The Company collects information as described below. The Company uses information that we collect to create accounts; fulfill requests for the Service; improve our website, products and Service; contact Developers; conduct research; create reports for internal use and to fulfill the actions described below. Some specific types of information that the Company may collect and use (directly or through our third party service providers) include but are not limited to the following:

1.              From Developers. If you are an Developer, we may collect the following:

a.              Your name or your company name, your email, App name and App platform(s), and other information as required to access the Service. We use this information to facilitate the relationship between the Service and you as a Developer using the Service.

b.              Cookies. The Company uses "cookies" to keep and track your information. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate the Website. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We set a persistent cookie to store your password if you choose "auto login" so that you don't have to enter it more than once. We also store your display resolution and whether JavaScript is enabled in your browser to enhance your user experience. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's help file. However, removing cookies may result in you not being able to take full advantage of the features of the Service.

c.              Web Beacons. The Company uses web beacons to keep and track your information. A "web beacon" is an electronic image placed in the code of a web page. We use web beacons to monitor the traffic patterns of users from one page to another and to improve overall site performance.

2.              From End-Users. If you are using an App created using the Service, the Company may collect the following:

a.              Device-Specific Information. Device-specific information includes the following information about an End-User’s device: a hashed version of the unique device ID assigned to your iOS device, a hashed version of the device identifier associated with your Android or Windows Phone device, platform type and version (e.g. iOS v4, Android, etc.), hardware and processor type, screen resolution and human-readable description. The Company may use a one-way algorithm to hash IDs—the hashed versions of device IDs that the Company stores may not be converted back to recognizable device ID.

b.              App-Specific Information. App-specific information is information about each End-User and the App they are using. This information may include App name, user ID, data related to downloading the app, data related to authorization within the app, device-specific information as defined in the preceding section, total sessions and duration, and geo-location data. The Company may share App-specific information with the Developer who owns the App.

c.              Analytics Data. When you click on or look at certain items, we may store the data and use it for our internal analytics to improve our Service. This information includes but is not limited to the session ID, user ID or username, and session length. We may share all or some of this analytics data with Developers. Additional data may be collected in the future with or without notice.

3.              From Developers and End-Users. We may collect the following from any aforementioned individual:

a.              Information You Provide. If you provide us feedback or contact us via e-mail, we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content included in the e-mail, in order to send you a reply. When you participate in one of our surveys, we may collect additional profile information.

b.              Third Party Tools. The Service may also contain third party tracking tools from our service providers (e.g. Google Analytics). Such third parties may use cookies, APIs and SDKs in our services to enable them to collect and analyze End-User information on our behalf. While a third party may have access to your personal information in connection with the performance of the Service, it may not use such information for any purpose other than providing its services.

c.              Anonymous Information. We may create anonymous information records from personal information by excluding information (such as your name) that make the data personally identifiable to you. We use this anonymous information to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of our website, products and services. The Company reserves the right to use anonymous information for any purpose and disclose anonymous information to third parties in its sole discretion.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure** ****

The Company does not rent, sell, or share personally identifiable information about Developers or End-Users with other people or companies which are not affiliates of the Company, except when we have your permission, as described above, or under the following circumstances:

1.              Service Providers. We may provide your information to third party vendors, including third party publishers and other service providers, who work on behalf of the Company and need the information to do work for the Company. These third party vendors are required not to use your personal information other than to provide the services requested by the Company.

2.              Other Disclosures. Regardless of any choices you make regarding your personal information (as described below), the Company may disclose personal information (a) to respond to subpoenas, warrants, court orders, lawful requests or legal process; (b) to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or protect our customers; (c) in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud or as otherwise required by law; or (d) to investigate any violation of this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Service.

3.              Affiliates. We may share some or all of your personal information with our current or any future parent company, any subsidiaries, or other companies under a common control, in which case we will require our affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

4.              Acquirer. We may transfer information about you if the Company is acquired by or merged with another entity. The successor entity will possess the personal information collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

5.              Anonymous Information. As described above, we may share anonymous information about Developers (and/or End-Users if applicable) with any third parties, including our advertisers, publishers, business partners and sponsors.

**Choices** ****

1.              Opting Out of Marketing

a.              We may periodically send Developers free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote the use of our Service. When you receive newsletters or promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive or by contacting us at privacy@GetSocialize.com.

b.              As described above, we may disclose End-User information to Developers for their own marketing purposes; however, we will cease any further disclosure of End-User information to Developers for their own direct marketing purposes if you “opt-out” by contacting us at privacy@GetSocialize.com.

c.              Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you service related communication, including notices of any updates to our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy.

2.              Changes and Deletion of Your Data

a.              Developers may change any of their personal information in their accounts by editing their profiles within their accounts on the Website. They can contact the Company at any time at privacy@GetSocialize.com if they would like the Company to deactivate their accounts. Please note that the Company may not be able to entirely delete an account due to the data associated with the account and necessary for the Company’s archives.

**Information Protection**

The Company uses reasonable efforts to protect End-Users’ and Developers’ personal information against unauthorized access and unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. However, the Company cannot guarantee that this personal information will be absolutely protected. For example, this personal information may be affected by actions outside of the Company’s control, such as computer "hacking" and physical theft. Both Developers and End-Users acknowledge that they provide their personal information at their own risk.

**Our Privacy Policy About Children** ****

The Company does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If Developers are under 13, they should not attempt to register or send any information about themselves to the Company, including their names, addresses, telephone numbers or email addresses. No one under the age of 13 may provide any personal information. Developers must take every reasonable precaution to ensure that their End-Users are 13 years old or older.In the event that the Company learns that it has collected personal information from a child under age 13, the Company will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that the Company might have any information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us at privacy@GetSocialize.com.

**International Transfer** ****

For both Developers and End-Users, the Company may transfer information that we collect about you (including personal information) to affiliated entities, to other third parties across borders, or from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. and the use and disclosure of information about you, including personal information, as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy** ****

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if the Company makes any material changes in the way it uses personal information, the Company will notify Developers by sending them an e-mail to the last e-mail address they provided to the Company and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Website. It is the responsibility of the Developers to make their End-Users aware of any such changes.Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately. Please note that at all times Developers are responsible for updating their personal information to provide the Company with their most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail address that an Developer has provided is not valid or for any reason is not capable of delivering to an Developer the notice described above, the dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice.In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect the Company’s use of personal information that Developers provided prior to notification of such changes. If Developers do not wish to permit changes in the Company’s use of their personal information, they must request deactivation of their accounts and cease using the Website or Service. Continued use of he Website or Service following notice of such changes shall indicate acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

**Contact Information** ****

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at:Socialize, Inc.  
Privacy Policy Issues  
153 Townsend St. Suite 9057  
San Francisco, CA 94107  
_privacy@GetSocialize.com_
